Contact

monlecca@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/bryan-pelletier-8a9271b9 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare
Customer Service
Microsoft Excel

Bryan Pelletier

OR RN at U.S. Department of Veterans Affairs

Raleigh-Durham, North Carolina Area

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Operating room nursing, Communication, Patient Support, Team Building, and U.S. Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA). Strong healthcare services professional with a Associate of Science (AS) focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from Capital Community College and a Bachelors of Science Healthcare Management from Charter Oak State College. Registered nurse with background experience in operating room, informatics, consulting, and project management.

Experience

U.S. Department of Veterans Affairs 1 year 6 months

OR RN

December 2019 - Present (8 months)

Raleigh-Durham, North Carolina Area

O.R. RN

February 2019 - December 2019 (11 months)

Charleston, South Carolina

Medical University of South Carolina O.R. RN

November 2018 - February 2019 (4 months)

Charleston, South Carolina

Soliant Health

Travel Operating Room R.N.

April 2017 - October 2018 (1 year 7 months)

Middlesex Hospital

Operating Room R.N.

April 2015 - November 2017 (2 years 8 months)

UConn Health

11 years 8 months

Systems Coordinator

March 2015 - April 2017 (2 years 2 months)

Admin. & Clinical Sys. Coordinator

March 2014 - March 2015 (1 year 1 month)

Operating Room R.N.

September 2010 - March 2014 (3 years 7 months)

Pharmacy Technician

September 2005 - September 2010 (5 years 1 month)

Education

Capital Community College

Associate of Science (AS), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse

Charter Oak State College

Bachelor of Science - BS, Health/Health Care Administration/Management